mailfoogae.appspot.com 2014-08-31

# Streak - CRM in your Inbox

## Privacy

### **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form. Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

### **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our service based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service and support needs)

### **Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

### **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personal information except in accordance with this policy. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

### **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

### **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

### **Feedback**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using: [support@streak.com](mailto:support@streak.com)

Gmail is a registered trademark of Google. Streak is not affiliated with Google or Gmail.
